ABHIK DAS 8967716359 abhikdas928@gmail.com

Team Leader and QA Nov 13 -2022- 21- March-2023 Worked as a Trainer and job role was to Train people on how to work with the combination of skillset and using software skills. Tech Support and providing resolution, and possess a positive attitude. Aiming to use my proven skills to effectively fill any given role in your company.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

<u>INTELLIGENT IMAGE MANAGEMENT LIMITED</u> – Team Leader and quality analyst Nov-13 -2022 - 21 Mar 2023 Worked as a Team leader and quality analyst job role was to Train people on how to work with the combination of skillset and using software skills through online mode of communication. Also to check the quality of the work and execute work properly as a QA

- . Providing Training to the Incoming trainees using the online mode of communication.
- . Explaining the module and taking them through the module before hand over to the production.
- . Also showing how to work using the modules and software's provided by the company.

<u>LIFE INSURANCE CORPORATION OF INDIA</u> / LIC INDIA / Insurance Advisor Agent and Customer Relations / JULY 2019– JULY 2021

- Selling Policies daily, with duties including signing up new customers, retrieving customer policies presenting relevant policy information.
- · Entering customer data and Organizing customer interaction logs
- Received an average 85% customer satisfaction rating as per Customer Experience and their feedbacks
- · Research complicated cases without prompting to provide more comprehensive service to customers

EDUCATION

IGNOU UNIVERSITY
Bachelor Of Arts In English - 2016

HIGHER SECONDARY
National Institute Of Opening Schooling - 2012

SECONDARY
Central Board Of Secondary Education - 2010

<u>SKILLS</u>

- Can Handle quarries.
- Experience with Microsoft Office Word & Excel also power point
- Excellent communication skills with a focus on on any given role.
- 45 WPM Typist
- Problem solving and quick solution expert
- Bilingual in English Hindi and Bengali